<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Dr Simon Wells</title>
    <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Dr Simon Wells</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2001-2018 - Simon Wells</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.simonwells.org/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Paper at CMNA&#39;21</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2021.09.01_cmna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2021.09.01_cmna/</guid>
      <description>My latest paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Towards a Declarative Approach to Constructing Dialogue Games&amp;rdquo;, will be presented at the upcoming 21st International Workshop in Computational Models of Natural Argument (CMNA&#39;21).
The paper is joint work with Mark Snaith from RGU in which we sketch out a new programme of research into how dialogue games, expressed using a new sub-unit of the DGDL called &amp;ldquo;fragments&amp;rdquo;, can be re-used in new contexts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Paper in Computer Graphics Forum</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2021.08.12_cgf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2021.08.12_cgf/</guid>
      <description>My latest paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Design and Evaluation of Visualization Techniques to Facilitate Argument Exploration&amp;rdquo;, with my recently graduated Ph.D student, Dr Dana Khartabil, and colleagues from Edinburgh Napier University, Edinburgh University, and Ontario Tech University, has just been published in the Computer Graphics Forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk on AI Research at Edinburgh Napier University for the SICSA-AI all hands meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2021.06.17_sicsaai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2021.06.17_sicsaai/</guid>
      <description>A brief overview of AI resarch activities at Edinburgh Napier University. This is not an exhaustive survey but is broadly indicative of the breadth and depth of AI related activities carried out at ENU, primarily within the School of Computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk at the Twentieth Computational Models of Natural Argument Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.09.08_cmna20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.09.08_cmna20/</guid>
      <description>I presented a talk to the delegates of the twentieth Computational Models of Natural Argument Workshop on the subject of &amp;ldquo;Datastores for Argumentation Data&amp;rdquo; in which he talked about SADFace &amp;amp; the ArgDB as a way to store and manipulate argumentative datasets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo at the 8th International Conference on Computational Models of Argument</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.09.08_comma2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.09.08_comma2020/</guid>
      <description>I presented work in a demo at COMMA 2020 on the subject of &amp;ldquo;The Open Argumentation PLatform (OAPl)&amp;rdquo; in which I talked the various pieces of software (some more mature, some more exploratory and prototypical) which form the inital tranch of contributions to a nascent Open Platform for Argumentation Software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk at the Third Trust In Intelligent Machines Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.05.27_third-trust-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.05.27_third-trust-workshop/</guid>
      <description>I presented a talk to the delegates of the third Trust in Intelligent Machines Workshop. The subject of my talk was on the various shaded of grey, or lack of clarity, in considering the issue of trust in the context of intelligent machines, communication, and dialogue when deception is an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECA Paper on Partisan Political Argument in the online Brexit Campaign</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;partisan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;partisan/</guid>
      <description>At the recent Third European Conference on Argumentation (ECA) I presented a paper entitled &amp;ldquo;A Paroxysm of Dissent: Partisan Political Advertising During the Brexit Campaign&amp;rdquo;. The paper is about the online advertisements used within the Brexit campaign prior to the 2016 referendum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribution to the ECA Symposium on Argument Strength</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;strength/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;strength/</guid>
      <description>I contributed to the Symposium on Argument Strength at the recent Third European Conference on Argumentation (ECA). The symposium was organised by Frank Zenker and other contributions were from to Marcin Selinger, Kamila Debowska-Kozlowska, and David Godden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Published in the Proceedings of ISSA 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.04.05_issa&#43;proceedings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.04.05_issa&#43;proceedings/</guid>
      <description>Together with my colleague, Al Baker, I published a paper in the proceedings of the 9th Conference of the International Society for the Study of Argumentation hosted by the University of Amsterdam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting Intelligent Machines: Deepening Trust Within Socio-Technical Systems</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.07_ieee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.07_ieee/</guid>
      <description>Together with the other delegates from the first TIM workshop earlier in the year, I&amp;rsquo;ve published a paper in the IEEE Technology and Society Magazine entitled &amp;ldquo;Trusting Intelligent Machines: Deepening Trust Within Socio-Technical Systems&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop on Intelligent Machines &amp; Human Behaviour</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.06_imhb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.06_imhb/</guid>
      <description>With colleagues from the Leeds University &amp;amp; UCL, I am organising a workshop on Intelligent Machines &amp;amp; Human Behaviour which is to be hosted at the 2019 AISB Annual Convention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Society for the Study of Argumentation (ISSA) Conference 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.07.06_issa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.07.06_issa/</guid>
      <description>Together with my colleague, Al Baker, I presented a paper at the 9th Conference of the International Society for the Study of Argumentation hosted by the University of Amsterdam. Our paper is on the theme of lying machines and investigates the question of when a machine should be able to lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SICSA Reasoning, Learning, &amp; Explainability (ReaLX) Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</guid>
      <description>I presented a paper at the SICSA AI Theme workshop on Reasoning, Learning, &amp;amp; Explainability (ReaLX) hosted by Robert Gordon University in Aberdeen. My paper was on the subject of argumentative dialogue protocols and argumentation schemes as a fundamental and humane framework for achieving composable and explainable AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust In Intelligent Machines Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Along with my colleagues, Simon Powers &amp;amp; Cedric Perret, we are hosting a workshop at Edinburgh Napier University&amp;rsquo;s Sighthill campus on the topic of &amp;ldquo;Trust in Intelligent Machines&amp;rdquo;. Our broad goal is to explore some of the issues and probelms associated with increasing delegation of decision making to artificially intelligent machines where the outcomes affect the well being of humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ph.D Studentship in Argument Mining</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</guid>
      <description>Argument Mining, the process of detecting, reconstructing, and extracting argument structure from natural language sources has become a hot topic in Argumentation research in recent years. This is a challenging, multi-disciplinary arena whose questions go to the heart of classical Artificial Intelligence problems related to Knowledge Representation and Natural Language Processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Dark Patterns in Persuasive Technology Workshop @ Persuasive 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</guid>
      <description>With my colleagues, Prof. Agnis Stibe (Paris ESLSCA Business School, France), Dr. Kate Pangbourne (University of Leeds, UK), Dr. Brian Cugelman (AlterSpark, Toronto, ON, Canada), and Anne-Kathrine Kjær Christensen (Specifii, Copenhagen, Denmark) we ran a workshop on Dark Patterns in Persuasive technology at the Persuasive 2018 Conference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>