<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Dr Simon Wells</title>
    <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Dr Simon Wells</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2001-2018 - Simon Wells</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.simonwells.org/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SICSA Reasoning, Learning, &amp; Explainability (ReaLX) Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</guid>
      <description>I presented a paper at the SICSA AI Theme workshop on Reasoning, Learning, &amp;amp; Explainability (ReaLX) hosted by Robert Gordon University in Aberdeen. My paper was on the subject of argumentative dialogue protocols and argumentation schemes as a fundamental and humange framework for achieving composable and explainable AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust In Intelligent Machines Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Along with my colleagues, Simon Powers &amp;amp; Cedric Perret, we are hosting a workshop at Edinburgh Napier University&amp;rsquo;s Sighthill campus on the topic of &amp;ldquo;Trust in Intelligent Machines&amp;rdquo;. Our broad goal is to explore some of the issues and probelms associated with increasing delegation of decision making to artificially intelligent machines where the outcomes affect the well being of humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ph.D Studentship in Argument Mining</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</guid>
      <description>Argument Mining, the process of detecting, reconstructing, and extracting argument structure from natural language sources has become a hot topic in Argumentation research in recent years. This is a challenging, multi-disciplinary arena whose questions go to the heart of classical Artificial Intelligence problems related to Knowledge Representation and Natural Language Processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Dark Patterns in Persuasive Technology Workshop @ Persuasive 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</guid>
      <description>With my colleagues, Prof. Agnis Stibe (Paris ESLSCA Business School, France), Dr. Kate Pangbourne (University of Leeds, UK), Dr. Brian Cugelman (AlterSpark, Toronto, ON, Canada), and Anne-Kathrine Kjær Christensen (Specifii, Copenhagen, Denmark) we ran a workshop on Dark Patterns in Persuasive technology at the Persuasive 2018 Conference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>