<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr Simon Wells</title>
    <link>http://www.simonwells.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dr Simon Wells</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2001-2018 - Simon Wells</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.simonwells.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/publications/</guid>
      <description>S. Wells (2019) &#34;A Paroxysm of Dissent: Partisan Political Advertising During the Brexit Campaign&#34;
Abstract for paper presented at the 3rd European Conference on Argumentation: Reason to Dissent (ECA19), Groningen, NL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/projects/</guid>
      <description>SUStainable and PERsuasive Human Users moBility in future cities (SUPERHUB) – A large EU FP7 IP project.  [STATUS: PROJECT COMPLETED 30th November 2014]  The Dialogue Game Description Language (DGDL), a domain specific language and supporting toolkit for describing the rules of diverse dialectical games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/talks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Shades of Grey || Some Thoughts on the subject of intelligent machines, trust, communiation, and deception&amp;rdquo;, presented at the third Trust in Intelligent Machines Workshop (TIM 2020), Online, on Wednesday 27th May 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Current Taught Courses &amp;amp; Modules I am Module Leader for the following modules:
 SET08101: Web Tech SET08114: Mobile Application Development SET09103: Advanced Web Tech SET09117: Algorithms &amp;amp; Data Structures  I also supervise honours, masters, and phd projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: s.wells@napier.ac.uk Landline: 0131 455 2893  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/bio/</guid>
      <description>Simon Wells is a lecturer in the School of Computing at Edinburgh Napier University.
His research interests lie generally in Artificial Intelligence with a specific focus on reasoning, decision-making, and strategic interaction achieved via formal and applied argumentation-based techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk at the Third Trust In Intelligent Machines Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.05.27_third-trust-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2020.05.27_third-trust-workshop/</guid>
      <description>I presented a talk to the delegates of the third Trust in Intelligent Machines Workshop. The subject of my talk was on the various shaded of grey, or lack of clarity, in considering the issue of trust in the context of intelligent machines, communication, and dialogue when deception is an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECA Paper on Partisan Political Argument in the online Brexit Campaign</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;partisan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;partisan/</guid>
      <description>At the recent Third European Conference on Argumentation (ECA) I presented a paper entitled &amp;ldquo;A Paroxysm of Dissent: Partisan Political Advertising During the Brexit Campaign&amp;rdquo;. The paper is about the online advertisements used within the Brexit campaign prior to the 2016 referendum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribution to the ECA Symposium on Argument Strength</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;strength/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.06.27_eca&#43;strength/</guid>
      <description>I contributed to the Symposium on Argument Strength at the recent Third European Conference on Argumentation (ECA). The symposium was organised by Frank Zenker and other contributions were from to Marcin Selinger, Kamila Debowska-Kozlowska, and David Godden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Published in the Proceedings of ISSA 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.04.05_issa&#43;proceedings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2019.04.05_issa&#43;proceedings/</guid>
      <description>Together with my colleague, Al Baker, I published a paper in the proceedings of the 9th Conference of the International Society for the Study of Argumentation hosted by the University of Amsterdam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusting Intelligent Machines: Deepening Trust Within Socio-Technical Systems</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.07_ieee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.07_ieee/</guid>
      <description>Together with the other delegates from the first TIM workshop earlier in the year, I&amp;rsquo;ve published a paper in the IEEE Technology and Society Magazine entitled &amp;ldquo;Trusting Intelligent Machines: Deepening Trust Within Socio-Technical Systems&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop on Intelligent Machines &amp; Human Behaviour</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.06_imhb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.12.06_imhb/</guid>
      <description>With colleagues from the Leeds University &amp;amp; UCL, I am organising a workshop on Intelligent Machines &amp;amp; Human Behaviour which is to be hosted at the 2019 AISB Annual Convention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Society for the Study of Argumentation (ISSA) Conference 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.07.06_issa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.07.06_issa/</guid>
      <description>Together with my colleague, Al Baker, I presented a paper at the 9th Conference of the International Society for the Study of Argumentation hosted by the University of Amsterdam. Our paper is on the theme of lying machines and investigates the question of when a machine should be able to lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SICSA Reasoning, Learning, &amp; Explainability (ReaLX) Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</guid>
      <description>I presented a paper at the SICSA AI Theme workshop on Reasoning, Learning, &amp;amp; Explainability (ReaLX) hosted by Robert Gordon University in Aberdeen. My paper was on the subject of argumentative dialogue protocols and argumentation schemes as a fundamental and humane framework for achieving composable and explainable AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust In Intelligent Machines Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Along with my colleagues, Simon Powers &amp;amp; Cedric Perret, we are hosting a workshop at Edinburgh Napier University&amp;rsquo;s Sighthill campus on the topic of &amp;ldquo;Trust in Intelligent Machines&amp;rdquo;. Our broad goal is to explore some of the issues and probelms associated with increasing delegation of decision making to artificially intelligent machines where the outcomes affect the well being of humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ph.D Studentship in Argument Mining</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</guid>
      <description>Argument Mining, the process of detecting, reconstructing, and extracting argument structure from natural language sources has become a hot topic in Argumentation research in recent years. This is a challenging, multi-disciplinary arena whose questions go to the heart of classical Artificial Intelligence problems related to Knowledge Representation and Natural Language Processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Dark Patterns in Persuasive Technology Workshop @ Persuasive 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</guid>
      <description>With my colleagues, Prof. Agnis Stibe (Paris ESLSCA Business School, France), Dr. Kate Pangbourne (University of Leeds, UK), Dr. Brian Cugelman (AlterSpark, Toronto, ON, Canada), and Anne-Kathrine Kjær Christensen (Specifii, Copenhagen, Denmark) we ran a workshop on Dark Patterns in Persuasive technology at the Persuasive 2018 Conference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>