<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr Simon Wells</title>
    <link>http://www.simonwells.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dr Simon Wells</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2001-2018 - Simon Wells</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.simonwells.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/publications/</guid>
      <description>S. Wells &amp; A. Baker (2018) &#34;Lying in Real World Argumentative Dialogue Systems&#34;
Abstract for paper presented at the 9th Conference of the International Society for the Study of Argumentation (ISSA), University of Amsterdam, NL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/projects/</guid>
      <description>SUStainable and PERsuasive Human Users moBility in future cities (SUPERHUB) – A large EU FP7 IP project. [STATUS: PROJECT COMPLETED 30th November 2014]
 The Dialogue Game Description Language (DGDL), a domain specific language and supporting toolkit for describing the rules of diverse dialectical games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/talks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;MIND THE GAPS: Deception in real world argumentative dialogue systems&amp;rdquo;, presented at the 9th Conference of the International Society for the Study of Argumentation (ISSA), University of Amsterdam, NL, on Friday 6th July 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Current Taught Courses &amp;amp; Modules I am Module Leader for the following modules:
 SET08101: Web Tech SET08114: Mobile Application Development SET09103: Advanced Web Tech SET09117: Algorithms &amp;amp; Data Structures  I also supervise honours, masters, and phd projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: s.wells@napier.ac.uk Landline: 0131 455 2893  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/bio/</guid>
      <description>Simon Wells is a lecturer in the School of Computing at Edinburgh Napier University.
His research interests lie generally in Artificial Intelligence with a specific focus on reasoning, decision-making, and strategic interaction achieved via formal and applied argumentation-based techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SICSA Reasoning, Learning, &amp; Explainability (ReaLX) Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.06.27_realx/</guid>
      <description>I presented a paper at the SICSA AI Theme workshop on Reasoning, Learning, &amp;amp; Explainability (ReaLX) hosted by Robert Gordon University in Aberdeen. My paper was on the subject of argumentative dialogue protocols and argumentation schemes as a fundamental and humange framework for achieving composable and explainable AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust In Intelligent Machines Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.06_first-trust-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Along with my colleagues, Simon Powers &amp;amp; Cedric Perret, we are hosting a workshop at Edinburgh Napier University&amp;rsquo;s Sighthill campus on the topic of &amp;ldquo;Trust in Intelligent Machines&amp;rdquo;. Our broad goal is to explore some of the issues and probelms associated with increasing delegation of decision making to artificially intelligent machines where the outcomes affect the well being of humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ph.D Studentship in Argument Mining</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.04_advert_2018-05-31/</guid>
      <description>Argument Mining, the process of detecting, reconstructing, and extracting argument structure from natural language sources has become a hot topic in Argumentation research in recent years. This is a challenging, multi-disciplinary arena whose questions go to the heart of classical Artificial Intelligence problems related to Knowledge Representation and Natural Language Processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.03_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.05.03_update/</guid>
      <description>A new look but the same content. Moved from a hand-generated static site that had served me well for nearly ten years to a Hugo generated static site. The design is modern and clean and should be a little easier to keep up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Dark Patterns in Persuasive Technology Workshop @ Persuasive 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.simonwells.org/news/2018.04.17_dark.patterns.workshop/</guid>
      <description>With my colleagues, Prof. Agnis Stibe (Paris ESLSCA Business School, France), Dr. Kate Pangbourne (University of Leeds, UK), Dr. Brian Cugelman (AlterSpark, Toronto, ON, Canada), and Anne-Kathrine Kjær Christensen (Specifii, Copenhagen, Denmark) we ran a workshop on Dark Patterns in Persuasive technology at the Persuasive 2018 Conference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>